[line ringing]
[man] It's me.
I found her.
She's coming to Seoul.
but not for long.
I have to go after her.
[♪ The Killers:
"Mr. Brightside"]
♪ Chest now. he takes off her ♪
♪ Dress now. let me go ♪
♪ And I just can't look ♪
♪ It's killing me ♪
♪ They're taking control ♪
Okay. Okay. okay.
♪ Jealousy ♪
♪ Turning saints into the sea ♪
♪ Swimming through
sick lullabies ♪
♪ Choking on your alibis ♪
♪ But it's just
the price I pay ♪
♪ Destiny is calling me ♪
♪ Open up my eager eyes ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm Mr. Brightside...
[whooping. applause. cheering]
[laughing]
[whooping and cheering continue]
[speaking Korean] Your
friend's got a good voice!
-Isn't he your friend?
-Huh?
-Cheers!
-[♪ Backstreet Boys: "I Want It That Way"]
♪ Apart ♪
♪ Can't reach to ♪
-♪ Your heart ♪
-[clears throat]
-♪ When you say ♪
-Where're you going?!
-♪ That I want it that way ♪
-[speaking English] More soju!
♪ Tell me why ain't
nothing but a heartache ♪
♪ Tell me why ain't nothing
but a big mistake...
[suspenseful music playing]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Status?
All clear. Target's in position.
Security presence will be heavy.
[indistinct chatter]
-[man] Yeah?
-[woman] Yeah.
[line ringing]
[Atwood] Target's on the ninth
floor of the Conrad Hotel.
Mission's a go.
-[horn honks]
-[indistinct crowd chatter]
[Rebecca] Thank you so
much for taking the time.
I know you sent me the photos.
but I just really wanted
to see the space in person.
Oh. What's going on?
Mikhail Karpov is
giving interviews today.
Who's that?
Russia's ambassador
to South Korea.
He's one of... [quietly]
Putin's best friends.
[both laugh]
This is our most popular
set for a baby shower.
But for a boy. you're gonna
like this color rather than...
I'm so sorry. I have to
use the ladies' room.
[laughing] It's just
one of the many joys.
[indistinct crowd chatter]
[softly wheezing]
-Oh. no.
-Miss.
-Are you okay?
-Oh. Oh. I'm so sorry.
-Sit down. please.
-Yeah. I was feeling faint. I...
-Can I call a doctor?
-No. no. no. please. I just...
Low blood sugar. I think.
Is there any way that you could
get me something sweet to drink?
Maybe. um. juice?
-Of course. Yeah.
-Thank you.
[sighs]
[pulsing. suspenseful
music playing]
[men speaking Russian]
[phone ringing]
Oh. I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
-Are you American?
-Yes.
And you're not here with press?
No.
This area is off
limit to the public.
I-I'm so sorry.
I was faint. and I just...
I'll just go. Sorry.
One moment.
Hmm?
You forgot your juice.
Thank you.
[elevator bell dings]
-[man speaks Russian]
-[Karpov groaning]
[woman screams]
[panicked. overlapping
chatter in Russian]
Call an ambulance!
We need a doctor...
[elevator bell dings]
[woman yells in Russian]
Da. [speaks Russian]
[panicked chatter in Russian]
Who did this?! Who was with him?
Find them!
[woman whimpers]
There's a pregnant woman
heading downstairs!
Stop her!
[grunting]
[elevator bell dings]
-[guard grunts]
-[gasps]
[panting]
[♪ Blackpink: "Pretty Savage"]
[muffled groaning]
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Ah-ah ♪
[vocalist purrs]
♪ Blackpink in your area...
[guards shouting]
[bystanders screaming]
[Seo-Yeon whimpering]
[guard shouting in Russian]
[whimpering]
[guards shouting in Russian]
She's in the ballroom.
Make sure she can't get out...
-[Atwood] Talk to me.
-I'm in trouble.
Karpov's security has me pinned
inside the ninth floor banquet hall.
What are my exits?
[Atwood] There's a
set of service stairs
in the northwest
corner of the room.
but they lead to the lobby.
[doorknob rattling] -[guard
speaks Russian] -[guard 2 grunts]
[door rattling]
[exciting music playing]
[banging on door]
You got the wrong room!
[crowd chatter]
[gasping. shouting]
[speaking Russian]
She went out the window!
Check the street in
front of the hotel...
[knocking]
[David speaking Korean]
Come on. I brought the soju!
Stop fucking around and open up!
[speaking English] I said
you got the wrong room!
[grunting]
-[♪ "Dancing Queen"]
-[singers vocalizing]
[both grunting]
[thudding]
[groans. grunts]
♪ You can dance ♪
-[door closes]
-[panting]
[door opens]
[man and woman speaking Korean]
[guard speaking
Russian over radio]
[crowd chatter]
-[speaking Russian]
-[siren wailing]
[clears throat]
[beeps]
[passenger] Exfil
coordinates received.
En route to location now.
[tires squeal]
[phone buzzes]
[announcement in
Korean over P.A.]
[tense music playing]
[train chime plays
over speakers]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
-[tires squealing]
-[engine revving]
[lively chatter]
[panting]
-[sizzling]
-[lights buzzing]
-[David speaks Korean]
-[upset chatter]
♪ ♪
[tires squealing]
-Look out!
-[tires squeal]
Oh. my God! Oh. my God!
[baby crying]
[crying glitches. fades]
Shit. [grunts]
-[grunts]
-[sighs]
[engine idling]
[tense music playing]
[horn honks]
[indistinct chatter]
[siren wailing in distance]
[siren fades]
Come on.
-[exhales softly]
-Shit.
[tires squeal]
[gasping]
[shouting in Korean]
Okay. okay.
[speaking Korean]
Call for backup!
[tires squeal]
[officers shouting in Korean]
[atmospheric
electronic music plays]
[panting]
[footsteps approaching]
[ominous music playing]
[Juno] Hi. Manny.
You've looked better.
I don't know how long
you're gonna be conscious.
so I'll get to the point.
I know you betrayed me.
I know you tried to give sensitive
Caddis information to U.S. intelligence.
I want to know who
you were working with.
You're a piece of shit. Juno.
Selling out your own country.
my country. to help our enemies?
Did you really expect me
to go along with that?
I'm in the private
intelligence business.
The only enemy I have is peace.
You're a traitor.
The CIA will stop you.
The CIA?
Who do you think
taught me this shit?
Who were you working with?
[whimpers softly]
You were one of my best.
I'll make it simple.
You tell me what I want to know.
and I won't kill your family.
Sophie's got to be.
what. five by now?
You have ten seconds.
Time's up.
His name is...
...Jakub Dydek.
He's former Polish intelligence.
Where is he?
Marsaxlokk.
Fishing village on Malta.
[quietly] Okay.
What are you waiting for?
-I want a team on Malta within the hour.
-Okay.
[Oliver] Mother. can
we talk in private?
[Juno] Yes. please.
We've got a problem
with the Seoul op.
Karpov's dead. but
the exfil was hijacked
and someone's ambushed
three of our operatives.
Is Caddis exposed on this?
Local authorities are
on scene investigating.
but so far it isn't
being tied back to us.
-Are you sure?
-Mm-hmm.
Are you positive?
Mom. I said I'm sure.
Karpov was the only thing
linking us and the GRU.
If Langley finds out that we're
giving ally troop movements
to Russian intelligence. you.
me. Caddis. we lose everything.
I understand.
How about Rebecca? Is she okay?
Uh. well. we haven't been able to
make contact with her just yet.
-Okay. so find her now.
-Of course.
I can see how much
of a concern she is.
Rebecca just took out the
Sudanese finance minister
and his entire security detail.
She downed a Venezuelan
military aircraft
and people still think
it was engine failure.
If I'm concerned about Rebecca.
it's because she's the most
valuable asset in this organization.
Do we know who was behind
the Seoul sabotage?
No. only that it appears
to be a lone operative.
You're telling me
one person did this?
Well. they were
tactically trained. and...
...somehow it seems like they have
inside knowledge of our operation.
Okay. I want the entire
Seoul office on this.
I don't care what it takes. I want
this guy's head on a fucking platter.
Okay.
[lively chatter]
[tense music playing]
-[horn honks]
-[indistinct chatter]
[lint roller rolling]
[car alarm beeps]
♪ ♪
[turnstile beeps]
[announcement in
Korean over P.A.]
[quietly] Okay.
[sighs sharply]
[heartfelt music playing]
[train approaching]
[announcement in
Korean over P.A.]
[train chime plays
over speakers]
[sniffles]
[phone buzzes]
[speaking Korean] Hello?
[David over phone] Hey. it's me.
[exhales]
Did you find her?
Yes. but... something came up.
[speaking English] I
wasn't ID'd. I was careful.
but she got away before
I could make contact.
I'm sorry.
But I saw her. Eunju.
It's been nine years.
But it was her.
I know this is hard.
But it's time to come home.
I swear. I tried.
I came to the station.
I even bought a ticket.
but I am looking
at this train...
...and I can't get on.
We had a deal. David.
-I know.
-One shot. that's it.
That's all we decided to risk.
I know.
But she needs me.
If Caddis finds you.
they'll kill you.
They'll kill all of us.
I won't let that happen.
What if she can't be saved?
[indistinct chatter]
Hey... look. I-I need
you to pack your things
and get to the safe house. okay?
Don't tell anyone and
don't leave anything behind
that can be used to find you.
There's a train leaving
tomorrow at 3:00.
Please be on it.
I'll meet you in a day.
Two at the most.
[speaking Korean]
I'm sorry. Eunju.
[speaking English]
But she's my daughter.
I can't leave her again.
[dramatic music playing]
-[line ringing]
-[horn honking]
Hi. it's me.
Rebecca?
Where are you? Are you okay?
I'm somewhere in Itaewon.
I got away. but what
the fuck happened?
I was going to ask
you the same thing.
[scoffs] What's that
supposed to mean?
Atwood was attacked.
Police found
the exfil team beaten and
handcuffed in an alley.
so I'm asking you.
what happened?
Somebody knew.
fucking obviously.
Somebody found out
about the Karpov job
and hijacked the exfil team.
How?
You don't think that
I'm trying to find out?
This is my op.
-Juno.
-Yes. it was.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Wait. wait. wait.
So the exfil team gets
themselves caught.
and you're blaming me?
We have a major
intelligence breach
on the one mission I
cannot afford to have fail.
Right now I don't
know who to blame.
[contemplative music playing]
You don't trust me?
I'm on a plane to Korea. I
want answers when I land.
Jesus. Juno.
You're the one person in the
world who cares about me.
I wouldn't screw you over.
Someone did.
I'll find them and
I'll take care of it.
Make sure you do.
You're trusting her with this?
Rebecca's been on the job for four
years. She knows how to handle herself.
I think it's a mistake.
You want to talk about mistakes?
Where are we on the Seoul ID?
We were able to pull an image
from the security cameras
at the surveillance site.
but it doesn't ID him.
Korean male. late
40s. early 50s.
medium height. medium build.
Get this to our
contacts at Korea's NIS.
see if they can get
anything off it.
Did you tell Rebecca
why I put her on Karpov?
No.
She never cares why.
Good.
Don't.
But something
doesn't seem right.
[mysterious music playing]
[car alarm beeps]
[car alarm blaring]
♪ ♪
[Korean music playing
over speakers]
[speaking Korean] Come in.
Hey. man.
Your elder is here and you
don't even bother to get up?
[both chuckle]
My elder. huh?
What are you doing here?
I wanted some good noodles.
but your shop was
the only one open.
If you're going to insult me. at least
do it without that terrible accent.
What accent?
[laughs]
I can't understand a
word you're saying.
[both sigh]
[speaking English] Good
to see you. my friend.
Yeah. you. too.
How long has it been?
Two. three months?
I've been a little
busy these days.
Hmm...
[speaking Korean]
Sounds serious.
[speaking English]
Can we talk upstairs?
[speaking Korean]
I thought you quit.
My doctor told me I have a fatty
liver and need to stop drinking.
What are you going to do?
[speaking English]
Find another doctor.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
So. what's going on?
You helped me disappear
nine years ago.
I need you to do it again.
Someone found you?
-They will soon.
-Who?
Caddis.
Your own company?
Yeah. I may have founded
Caddis. but what they've become.
you know that's not me.
[sighs]
[laughing]
[laughing] What?
[speaking Korean] All you
had to do was be dead.
[speaking English]
How'd you fuck that up?
[chuckles]
Believe it or not. I chose this.
Why?
Because Caddis has something
of mine I want back.
Rebecca.
She's working for
them. Yong Shik.
As an assassin.
All these years. I
thought she was safe.
But now. knowing she's
working for Juno.
it's practically
a death sentence.
I can't just sit back
and let that happen.
And now you want to blow up
your life to get her back?
Wouldn't you?
[speaking Korean]
What about your wife?
[speaking English]
Does she feel the same?
[speaking Korean] That
would be nice. but...
[sighs]
[speaks Korean]
Will you help me?
[speaking English]
Give me a week.
I don't have a week.
I need new passports
within a day.
two at the most.
They won't be as good.
I just need them to be good
enough to get out of the country.
then we'll think of
a long-term plan.
Of course.
I'll send you payment and
photos as soon as I can.
When you're finished.
call me on this number.
You're not coming back. are you?
[sighs]
[somber music playing]
[speaks Korean]
Take care of your health.
Eat well.
[David chuckles]
As long as I don't eat your
noodles. I won't die. Don't worry.
[both chuckle]
-Yong Shik...
-Hmm?
...thank you so much.
[speaking English]
For everything.
[speaking Korean] It's cold
up here. Let's go inside.
[helicopter blades whirring]
Atwood.
One sec.
[pulsing music playing]
GPS coordinates.
♪ ♪
[door closes]
[♪ Artemas: "Ur Special to Me"]
♪ I need you to know ♪
♪ You're special to me ♪
♪ So special to me ♪
♪ Mm...
[both moaning]
Thanks. Atwood. I needed that.
[chuckles softly] Well.
now I just feel used.
[scoffs] Yeah. I could
tell how much you hated it.
[chuckles]
You know. we still have a little bit
of time left before it gets dark.
No. thanks.
[sighs]
You know what bothers me?
-Hmm?
-Whoever this guy is.
he didn't care about you.
he didn't care about Karpov.
he didn't care about the exfil team.
None of you guys were his target.
I was.
I want to know why.
[suspenseful music playing]
♪ ♪
[elevator bell chimes]
-[Moon] Good flight?
-Hmm.
-Are they ready for us downstairs?
-Yes. they are.
[phone ringing]
-[Juno] Did you find him?
-[Rebecca] Not yet.
but I know where he is.
What're you waiting for?
Coffee.
Atwood's getting me some.
I don't feel like you're
taking this seriously.
[Rebecca] Juno. you're
the closest thing I have
to family. and you just
told me you don't trust me.
I'm taking this
fucking seriously.
[Juno] How do you
know where he is?
GPS coordinates on the
back of a parking ticket.
I'm sending some hitters to back
you up. Oliver will coordinate.
He's off the bench?
Not exactly.
I'll have it done by
morning. I'll call you then.
-[Juno] Rebecca.
-What?
Careful with this one.
[suspenseful music playing]
♪ ♪
♪ Sometimes I get
a little lonely ♪
♪ So I took a one-way to
Atlanta to the homie ♪
♪ Everybody make assumptions ♪
♪ But I have to say there's
two sides to every story ♪
♪ I'm going all in.
no guts. no glory ♪
♪ Hey. boy. keep talking.
you gonna meet this 40 ♪
♪ We in Buckhead. we
rolling. rolling four deep ♪
♪ Ready. Freddy. feeling solid ♪
♪ I wake up every day ♪
♪ And I live like it's my last ♪
♪ Sometimes things
just move too fast ♪
♪ I wish I could slow it down ♪
♪ Hold me down. down ♪
♪ Down. hold it down. down ♪
♪ Put up and gonna call
me out. out. out ♪♪
[suspenseful music playing]
-Ready?
-Yeah.
[gun cocks]
♪ ♪
[explosion]
[man grunts]
[wheezing]
[tense music playing]
♪ ♪
He's running.
[intense music playing]
Split up. I'll look in here.
♪ ♪
-[shouts]
-[both grunting]
[shouts]
[grunting]
[grunts]
♪ ♪
-[gunshot]
-[shouts]
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
♪ ♪
[mysterious music playing]
[David] Rebecca.
[breathes shakily]
Dad?
[gasps]
You look...
You're so beautiful.
I th... I thought you...
You're alive?
You're fucking alive?!
Look.
I know this must be a
lot to take in right now.
All this time.
where have you been?
Nine years of my life.
You still haven't
put your gun down.
Neither have you.
I owe you answers. I know that.
But right now we have
to get out of here.
I'm not going anywhere
till you tell me.
-No. we have to leave.
-Tell me. tell me why you left
when I was 14 years old.
Tell me why you
made me an orphan.
[breathing shakily]
How could you do that?
How you could do that to me?
Everything I did.
I did to protect you.
[scoffs. pants]
You're a fucking liar.
I have to go.
And I want you to come with me.
That's what all
of this is about.
I can't lose you again.
But it's not my
decision. it's yours.
So you can either
come with me...
[sighs]
...or you can shoot me.
[contemplative music playing]
-[grunts]
-[panting]
I need to talk to her.
I don't give a fuck
who she's with.
I need to talk to her right now.
[indistinct chatter]
Did you know it was him?
What?
When you sent me after him.
did you know it was him?
-What are you talking about?
-Juno!
Don't lie to me.
Not about him.
Who are you talking about?
[sniffles]
My father.
He's alive?
[laughing]
Of all the sick shit...
Juno. did you send me
after my own father?
Tell me the truth. Juno.
Did you know?
No.
Say it.
I didn't know.
I swear to God.
[sobbing]
Listen. Rebecca.
Where is David now?
[sniffles]
He's here with me.
Are you safe?
Yeah. [sniffles]
Yeah! [crying]
We're gonna figure this
out together. okay?
You don't have to
make any decisions.
You don't have to do anything.
I'm sending a team for you.
And then I'm coming to you.
You're gonna be okay.
You understand?
[sobbing]
I have to go. He's getting up.
-Rebecca. wait...
-[line beeps]
[exhales]
[groans]
You hit me.
I was mad.
[grunts]
[mutters]
I'm bleeding.
Good.
Can you help me up?
[strained exhale]
I'm sorry.
[grunts]
[sniffles]
Should've led with that.
I love you.
And I missed you
more than you know.
[birds chirping. wings flapping]
No!
[somber music playing]
You okay?
♪ ♪
[shudders]
We have to go.
♪ ♪
I know you have questions.
Come with me and I'll
tell you everything.
♪ ♪
[tense music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm